Great work. Thumbs up. The data has landed safely on
our phones. But I was thinking about it, and actually
instead of hard coding our post code in, we'd really
[SOUND] like our sun train app user, to be able
to change their location in the settings. So let's make
the FetchWeatherTask more flexible by having it take as input
a postal code parameter. While we're doing that, we should
also take this opportunity to do a little bit of refactoring.
Instead of concatenating the strings for the server query
URL, we should use a UriBuilder Class to build
up he URL. We can declare a base URL
and then append each pair of query PARAM and
PARAM values onto it. This includes PARAM's for post
code. JSON format, metric units, and date count. This'll
make it easier in the future if we ever
have to make these options configurable by the user.
If you want to verify that the URL is built up properly. After
you do these tasks, you can use verbose logging to print it out.